7red.com 2016-11-08

# 7Red.com Casino - Privacy Statement

## 1\. Personal information being collected

When you create an account and browse / perform a gaming action on the site www.7red.com, 7Red will collect personal data about you. The responsible party for the collection of those data is the company 7Red registered in Curacao, and its offices are located at Dr Hugenholtzset z/n UTS Building, DSF Curacao and can be contacted by phone at 00 356 22 76 67 81.

“Personal data” refers to any data that identifies an individual including name, phone number, date of birth, email address, postal address and any other information that you choose to communicate to 7Red about yourself. Data collection is performed in accordance with both the Electronic Communications Privacy Directive (EC Directive/2002/58/EC) and the Curaçaoan Personal Data Protection Act (PDPA). To fight against fraud, 7Red is also likely to retain information relating to transactions on the site, including a truncated portion of credit card numbers used for such transactions as well as the expiry date.

## 2\. Purpose of data collection

Your personal data is collection for one or more of the following purposes:   
\- manage your activity on the site   
\- develop business statistics, conduct market and behaviour studies   
\- build and manage sales leads, including particularly technical operations such as standardisation, optimisation and duplication   
\- perform customer management operations   
\- send promotional information from 7Red. You can unsubscribe at any time to these offers by clicking on the link provided for this purpose at the bottom of the email concerned   
\- comply with our legal and regulatory obligations

## 3\. Recipients of data collection

7Red’s policy is not to sell any information related to its customers to third parties for commercial purposes. Only our company and our contracted partners for order processing have access to the information you provide us. The categories of persons who have access to your personal data in 7Red are within the limits of their respective duties, the sales department, administrative services, technical services and monitoring agencies (auditor, internal quality control procedures, etc). Recipients of your personal information may also include public bodies in order to meet legal obligations such as court officers, public officers and debt collection agencies.

## 4\. Consent

When you choose to communicate your personal information to the site, you expressly give your consent to the collection and use of your personal information in compliance with what has been stated in this charter and current laws.

## 5\. Security

We advise you to take every precaution to protect the security of your personal information and particularly, to prevent it from being distorted, damaged or that unauthorised parties have access to it.

## 6\. Control of Personal Information

If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as your zip code, phone, email or postal address), or if a user decides no longer to use our services, we provide a way to correct, update or deactivate that user's personally identifiable information provided to us. This can usually be done by emailing our Customer Support at support@7red.com. However, please understand that some information may not be deleted if we are required to store it for technical and/or legal reasons.

## 7\. Netent Privacy Policy

When playing casino slots developed by NetEnt, NetEnt’s privacy policy also applies. Click [here](https://www.netent.com/en/netent-privacy-policy-eu/) to read more.
